I'll complain about you!
سوف أشتكي منك!
(Ye Juncheng?)
(يي جونتشنغ؟)
(What's he wearing?)
(ماذا يرتدي؟)
(Why the lovely look?)
(لماذا المظهر الجميل؟)
(I didn't know this guy could be two-faced.)
(لم أكن أعرف أن هذا الرجل قد يكون ذا وجهين).
=My Honey=
= حبيبي =
=EP2 This Junior Boy Is Insane=
= EP2 هذا الفتى الصغير مجنون =
Ziying, are you all right?
زيينج ، هل أنت بخير؟
Here.
هنا.
We quit.
نحن نستقيل.
Complain as you wish.
تشكو كما يحلو لك.
Fine.
بخير.
I won't quit. I won't.
لن استسلم.  أنا لن.
Sorry. Sorry.
آسف.  آسف.
What are you talking about?
ما الذي تتحدث عنه؟
I'm terribly sorry.
أنا آسف للغاية.
Ziying, go.
زيينغ ، اذهب.
But I'm still working.
لكن ما زلت أعمل.
I won't quit.
لن استسلم.
I'm so sorry. I apologize.
أنا آسف جدا.  أنا أعتذر.
Don't.
لا.
Little bear, be a good girl.
أيها الدب الصغير ، كن فتاة طيبة.
Hey, don't leave.
لا ترحل.
Stay if you dare!
ابق إذا كنت تجرؤ!
Ye Juncheng,
يي جونتشنغ ،
what's wrong with you?
ما مشكلتك؟
Mr. Miser,
السيد مصر ،
what on earth are you up to?
ما الذي تنوي فعله بحق الأرض؟
Mr. Miser?
سيد مصر؟
What are you pretending?
ماذا تتظاهر؟
Never try to racketeer me, you know?
لا تحاول ابدا ابتزازي ، هل تعلم؟
What are you talking about?
ما الذي تتحدث عنه؟
Pretending you lost your memory?
التظاهر أنك فقدت ذاكرتك؟
Don't hold me up in making money.
لا تمسكني في كسب المال.
I get 800 yuan for two hours' work.
أحصل على 800 يوان مقابل عمل ساعتين.
I'm well paid.
أنا أحصل على أجر جيد.
I've got a better-paid job for you.
لدي وظيفة بأجر أفضل بالنسبة لك.
I wonder if you're interested.
أتساءل عما إذا كنت مهتمًا.
What is it? How much will you pay?
ما هذا؟  كم ستدفع؟
Tonight,
الليلة،
come and work in my apartment.
تعال واعمل في شقتي.
Who do you think I am?
من تظن انا؟
There are jobs that I don't do.
هناك وظائف لا أقوم بها.
8,000 yuan.
8000 يوان.
Let me make it clear first.
اسمحوا لي أن أوضحها أولا.
No skin contact.
لا يوجد ملامسة للجلد.
Mm.
مم.
Boss,
رئيس،
what would you like me to wear this time?
ماذا تريدين أن أرتدي هذه المرة؟
Just sit there quietly.
فقط اجلس هناك بهدوء.
You pay me 8,000 yuan
أنت تدفع لي 8000 يوان
but you don't need me to get changed?
لكنك لست بحاجة إلى أن أتغير؟
What villain asked you to get changed?
ما الشرير الذي طلب منك أن تتغير؟
He's so bad.
إنه سيء ​​للغاية.
(Andersen's Fairy Tales)
(حكايات أندرسن الخيالية)
(Is this a lullaby?)
(هل هذه تهويدة؟)
(Su Ziying, don't fall asleep.)
(سو زيينغ ، لا تنام.)
(Make your service worth 8,000 yuan.)
(اجعل خدمتك تساوي 8000 يوان.)
Sorry.
آسف.
I asked you not to touch me.
طلبت منك ألا تلمسني.
(It's really hard to earn 8,000 yuan.)
(من الصعب حقًا كسب 8000 يوان).
(What's wrong with him again?)
(ما مشكلته مرة أخرى؟)
(What happened?)
(ماذا حدث؟)
(Why am I back home without knowing anything?)
(لماذا أعود إلى المنزل دون معرفة أي شيء؟)
(Su Ziying?)
(سو زيينغ؟)
Is it the new trick to find a sugar daddy?
هل هي الحيلة الجديدة للعثور على أبي السكر؟
First, you slapped me without a reason
أولا ، لقد صفعتني بدون سبب
to have attracted my attention.
لجذب انتباهي.
Then you came to my home
ثم أتيت إلى منزلي
and threw yourself at me.
ورميت نفسك في وجهي.
Why don't you give a lecture to those rich ladies in disguise?
لماذا لا تلقي محاضرة لتلك السيدات الثريات المقنعات؟
You...
أنت...
You should have been an actor.
كان يجب أن تكون ممثلاً.
Pretending you lost your memory again?
التظاهر بأنك فقدت ذاكرتك مرة أخرى؟
Are you...
أنت...
Are you trying to welch on my pay?
هل تحاول دفع راتبي؟
Leave.
غادر.
Leave immediately.
غادر على الفور.
You make money by devious means.
أنت تكسب المال بوسائل خادعة.
Ye Juncheng, let go.
يي جونتشنغ ، اتركها.
You'll regret it.
سوف تندم عليها.
I asked you not to touch me.
طلبت منك ألا تلمسني.
Out!
خارج!
I charge by the hour.
أنا أتقاضى كل ساعة.
Pay me at least a little.
ادفع لي على الاقل قليلا
(It's happening again.)
(انه يحدث مجددا.)
(My heart hurts.)
(قلبي يتألم.)
Lin Han,
لين هان ،
don't worry.
لا تقلق.
I will only serve as a model.
سأعمل فقط كنموذج.
Mm. I'll hang up.
مم.  سوف أغلق الخط.
Hey, cutie.
مرحبًا يا حلوتي.
Come and have a chat with me.
تعال وتحدث معي.
Don't touch me.
لا تلمسني.
I'm just touching you, so what?
أنا فقط ألمسك ، وماذا في ذلك؟
I'm just doing it.
أنا فقط أفعل ذلك.
I'm gonna kill you!
سوف أقتلك!
Let go of me!
ترك لي!
Boss.
رئيس.
(There's someone you can never get away from or get rid of.)
(هناك شخص لا يمكنك الابتعاد عنه أو التخلص منه.)
(All rights of network communication reserved by Tencent)
(جميع حقوق اتصالات الشبكة محفوظة لشركة Tencent)